嘿 瑞秋 你知道怀孕的时候…
Hey, Rach, listen. Did you know that during pregnancy...
你的手指会肿成两倍大 而且再也不会消了吗
...your fingers swell up to twice their size and never go back?
天啊 让我看看
Oh, my God. Let me see that.
你每次都会上当
You fall for it every time.
我把我的旧孕妇装拿来给你
Hey. Look, I brought you my old maternity clothes.
菲比 那真的是太棒了 好可爱喔
Oh, Pheebs, that's so sweet. Oh, those are so cute.
你看 宝宝越长越大 它们也会跟着撑开来
And look. See how they expand as the baby grows?
宝宝出生后 可以穿它去偷西瓜
And then after the baby's born, they're great for shoplifting melons.
太好了 你们都在 感恩节 明天四点
Oh, good, you're all here. Okay, Thanksgiving tomorrow, 4:00.
你猜我邀请了谁 还记得高中同学威尔·卡佛特吗
Oh. And guess who I invited? Remember that guy Will Culvert from high school?
- 不   - 他跟罗斯同班
- No.     - He was in Ross' class.
他是仪队的 有点胖 他是个大胖子
Marching band, was kind of overweight. Well, really overweight.
我属于他瘦朋友那一群
I mean, I was his thin friend.
我不记得
Wow, I don't remember him.
你是说你假想的男朋友吗
Are you sure you're not talking about your imaginary boyfriend?
不 那是贾拉德
No, that was Jared.
我好久没有想起他了
Wow. Haven't thought about him in a long time.
威尔来城里出差
Anyway, um, Will's here on business...
他没地方可去 所以我邀请他过来
...and he didn't have a place to go so I invited him here.
那很好啊
Oh, that's nice.
他减肥成功
Oh, by the way, he's lost a bunch of weight.
他看起来很不错 好吧 他真的是帅呆了
I mean, he looks good. Okay, I mean really, really gorgeous.
- 我还爱着钱德   - 偶尔说一下不会要你命的
- I still love Chandler.     - Wouldn't hurt you to say it once in a while.
先说好了 今年我不煮火鸡…
Okay, also, just so you know, I'm not gonna make a turkey this year.
- 什么    - 菲比不吃火鸡
- What?     - Well, Phoebe doesn't eat turkey.
- 菲比   - 火鸡是漂亮聪明的动物
- Phoebe.     - Turkeys are beautiful, intelligent animals.
不是的 他们既丑又笨 也很好吃
No, they're not. They're ugly and stupid and delicious.
不只是菲比 威尔还在节食
All right, it's not just Phoebe. Will's still on a diet...
钱德不吃威恩节食物…
...Chandler doesn't eat Thanksgiving food...
瑞秋对家禽类反胃
...and Rachel's having her aversion to poultry.
是吗
She is?
对 记得吗 那天你吃鸡肉时我得走开
Yeah, remember I had to leave the other day when you had that chicken?
我以为那是因为我手里…
I thought that was just because I put the whole thing on my hand...
拿着鸡要他在桌上走的关系
...and made it walk across the table.
为了三个人做一只火鸡太不划算了
It just doesn't seem worth it to make a whole turkey for three people.
那真的很费功夫
It's a lot of work.
但感恩节一定要吃火鸡啊
But you gotta have turkey on Thanksgiving.
感恩节不吃火鸡 就像国庆日不吃苹果派
I mean, Thanksgiving with no turkey is like Fourth of July with no apple pie.
或是星期五不吃两个比萨
Or Friday with no two pizzas.
好吧 如果它真的对你很重要 但到时候一定会剩下很多
All right, fine, if it means that much to you, but there's gonna be a ton left over.
不 我发誓我会把那只火鸡吃完
No, there won't. I promise I will finish that turkey.
你是说你可以一次吃掉一整只火鸡
All right, you're telling me you can eat almost an entire turkey in one sitting?
没错 因为我是崔比亚尼家的人 这是我们的专长
That's right. Because I'm a Tribbiani. This is what we do.
我们不是伟大的思想家或世界领袖…
We may not be great thinkers or world leaders.
我们书念的不多 跑不快 但该死 我们是大胃王
We don't read a lot or run very fast, but damn it, we can eat.
# 没有人告诉你活着有多累 #
# So no one told you life was gonna be this way #
# 上班受罪 口袋空空 爱情变累赘 #
# Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's D.O.A. #
# 寂寞又潦倒 受气又受累 #
# It's like you're always stuck in second gear #
# 日复一日 年复一年 #
# When it hasn't been your day, #
# 时运不济 活着受罪 #
# your week, your month, or even your year #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# but I'll be there for you #
# 你我相偎相依 #
# 'Cause you're there for me too #
第四次长传 第三次18码
Four wide receivers. On third and 18.
明年桌边会坐一个宝宝
Hey, isn't it weird to think about how next year at this time...
感觉真的很奇怪吧
...there'll be a little baby at the table?
我是指瑞秋的孩子 但我很高兴你还有在听我说话
Rachel's. But good to know where you're at.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
- 感恩节快乐   - 你也是
- Happy Thanksgiving.     - You too.
- 需要我帮忙吗    - 好啊
- Anything I can do to help?     - Actually, there is.
通常钱德会帮忙 但他看球赛看得正入迷
Chandler usually helps but he's into the game so I don't wanna bother him.
- 麻烦你帮忙折餐巾   - 好的
- Could you help me fold these napkins?     - Sure.
我要去对面看看地瓜泥好了没
I'm gonna go across the hall to check on the yams.
- 好的   - 不 甜心 不是那样的
- Okay.     - No, no, no, sweetie. No, not like that.
我们不是在办农场舞会
We're not at a barn dance.
把它们折成天鹅的形状 我在圣诞节时教过你 记得吗
You wanna fold them like swans. Like I showed you at Christmas, remember?
记得 一切历历如新
Yeah, it all just came screaming back to me.
- 球赛还好看吗    - 我不知道
- So how's the game?     - I have no idea.
什么
What?
我假装看球赛 那样子就不必帮忙
Yeah, I'm just pretending to watch the game so I don't have to help out with stuff.
我不敢相信 这招太高明了
I don't believe you. That is brilliant.
- 摩妮卡不知道    - 对
- And Monica has no idea?     - Nope.
偶尔我会对着电视大叫
Every once in a while I just yell and scream stuff at the TV.
嘿 什么 啊
Hey, what...? Hey!
- 你的球队赢了吗    - 安德森刚刚又得分了
- Is your team winning, hon?     - Oh, yeah. Anderson just scored again.
根本就没有安德森这号人物
There's no Anderson.
我也想如法炮制 摩妮卡
Oh, I wanna get in on this. Hey, Mon?
我真的没办法帮你 我不知道球赛打到哪里了
I don't think I can't help you after all. I didn't realize this game was on.
- 你喜欢美式足球    - 通常我是不喜欢
- Oh. I didn't know you liked football.     - Well, normally, I don't.
但今天是绿湾队在比赛
But, you know, Green Bay is playing.
- 你喜欢绿湾队    - 那是我最喜欢的海湾
- You like Green Bay?     - Well, it's only like my favorite bay.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
- 感恩节快乐   - 谢谢
- Happy Thanksgiving.     - Aw, thanks.
威尔 我很高兴你能来 你看起来帅呆了
God, Will, I'm so glad that you came. You just... You look great.
你一定减掉了…
You must've lost like...
150磅
A hundred and fifty pounds.
我会是潜水艇三明治广告的下一号人选
Yeah, I'm gonna be in one of those Subway sandwich commercials.
- 是派   - 零脂肪 无糖 也没有奶
- A pie.     - Right. Uh, it's no fat, no sugar, no dairy.
- 它不好吃 丢了它   - 我来介绍你们认识
- It's no good. Throw it out.     - You wanna meet some people?
他是我丈夫钱德 他是威尔
This is, uh, my husband, Chandler. Chandler, this is Will.
我很想跟你握手 但我忙着看球赛
Oh, hey. I'd shake your hand but, uh, I'm really into the game.
而且我们两个只要不站在一起 就不会伤了我的自尊
Plus, I think it'd be better for my ego if we didn't stand right next to each other.
- 她是菲比   - 嗨
- This is Phoebe.     - Hi.
嘿 哇
Hey. Wow.
做的好
Well done.
- 你要帮我吗    - 当然
- Wanna give me a hand?     - Sure.
摩妮卡 我真的觉得你很漂亮
Monica, I can't get over how great you look. You look stunning.
你也很帅 你的身材真棒
You look incredible too. You're just so fit.
我在看球赛 但我没聋
I'm watching the game but I'm not deaf.
我一直想告诉你 罗斯也会来
Oh, um, I meant to tell you, Ross is coming.
太棒了 我喜欢罗斯
Ross is coming. Great, I love Ross.
很好 瑞秋·葛林也会来
Well, good. And Rachel Green too.
噢
Oh.
- 有问题吗    - 没有 没关系的
- Is there a problem?     - Nope. Uh, it's okay.
那只是…
It's just, uh...
天啊 我恨她
God, I hated her.
- 什么    - 我恨她
- What?     - I hated her.
高中时她对我很凶
She was horrible to me in high school.
但那是很久以前的事了 现在我很好
But hey, that was a long time ago. I'm in a good place.
或许再见到她会很有趣
It might be actually fun to see her again.
你有蛋糕或饼干吗
Got any cakes or cookies or something?
不 威尔
No, Will. No.
我们很久没大叫了 或许我们该大叫一下
You know, it's been a while since we screamed something. Maybe we should.
- 好吧 不    - 加油
- Oh, okay. No!     - Oh, come on!
该死的裁判 下地狱去吧
Damn you, ref. You burn in hell!
你在做什么
Hey, what are you doing? You gotta save room.
你还得吃掉一整只火鸡
You've got almost an entire turkey to eat.
让我跟你解释一下人体的运作方式
Let me explain to you how the human body works.
我得先让我的胃暖暖身
I have to warm up my stomach first.
- 吃薯片像是在做拉筋运动   - 好吧
- Eating chips is like stretching.     - Okay.
别担心 崔比亚尼永远吃不饱
Don't worry, Tribbianis never get full.
我知道你们在谈些什么
I actually know what you're talking about.
我要告诉你一件事
And I'm here to tell you something.
你可以吃个不停 但你无法填满内心的空虚
You can eat and eat and eat, but nothing will ever fill that void.
- 这家伙到底是谁 - 他是我们的高中同学威尔 他是乔伊
- Who the hell is this guy?     - This is Will, from high school.
- 嘿   - 哈罗
- Oh, hey.     - Hello.
- 威尔   - 罗斯
- Will.     - Ross.
你来了 天啊 你看起来棒极了 大帅哥
Hey, you came. Man, you look incredible. Hot stuff.
- 大帅哥    - 很高兴能见到你
- Hot stuff?     - It's good to see you, man.
我也是 你是做哪一行的
Yeah, you too. Man, so, what are you up to?
- 我是期货经纪人   - 听起来很有趣
- I'm a commodities broker.     - Really? That sounds interesting.
才怪
Yeah, it's not.
- 但我现在既有钱又苗条   - 喔
- But I'm rich and thin.     - Oh, hey.
自从兰西·戴维斯的毕业派对之后 我就没有见过你
Man, I don't think I've seen you since, uh, Lance Davis' graduation party.
- 那一晚真的很疯狂   - 对
- That was such a fun night.     - Yeah.
如果我们都有被邀请就好了 但那还是很疯狂
Would've been good if we had gotten in, but still, real fun.
那时我们逊呆了 你还记得我们多迷恐龙吗
God, we were lame back then. Do you remember how into dinosaurs we were?
- 对   - 你是做哪一行的
- Yeah.     - So, what do you do now?
你要在城里待多久
So how long are you in town?
- 嗨   - 嘿 甜心 太好了
- Hi.     - Hey, sweetie. Oh, good.
瑞秋·葛林
Rachel Green.
啊 对了 你没事吧
Oh, oh, that's right. Are you gonna be okay?
我没事 只是… 天啊 罗斯 我恨她
Oh, I'll be fine. It's just... God, I hate her, Ross. I hate her.
高中是很久以前的事了
Will, high school was a long time ago.
看看她拿着地瓜泥站在那里的样子
Look at her standing there with those yams.
我的两个死对头 瑞秋·葛林跟碳水化合物
- My two greatest enemies, Rachel Green and complex carbohydrates.
天啊 那是谁
Oh, my God, Monica. Who is that?
- 他是我们的高中同学威尔   - 我不记得他了
- That's Will, from high school.     - Ah. I do not remember him.
他真的越来越性感了
Wow, really got that sexy smoldering thing going on.
天啊 看他盯着我瞧的样子
Oh, my God. Look at the way he's just staring at me.
他用唇语跟我说话
I think he's trying to mouth something to me, but I can't make it out.
我恨你
I hate you.
- 好了 晚餐准备好了   - 好吧
- Okay, dinner's ready.     - Okay.
- 真的很精彩   - 谁赢了
- Yeah. Solid effort. Solid effort.     - Oh, so who won?
- 绿湾队   - 底特律队
- Green Bay.     - Detroit.
- 什么    - 技术上来说狮队赢了
- What?     - Well, the Lions technically won.
但在士气方面是绿湾美人鱼队赢了
But it was a moral victory for the Green Bay Mermen.
- 嗨 你是威尔吧   - 是的
- Hi. Will, right?     - Right.
嗨 我是瑞秋·葛林
Right, hi. I'm Rachel Green.
- 我记得你   - 真的吗 你真好
- Oh, I remember you.     - Really? Aren't you sweet?
我得告诉你 我真的很难记得你的样子
I gotta tell you though, I'm having the hardest time placing you.
等一下 我想我记得你
Oh, oh, hang on. I think I remember you.
我们在兰西·戴维斯的毕业派对上厮混过
Did we, um...? Did we fool around at Lance Davis' graduation party?
- 你真是不可思议   - 谢谢你
- You are unbelievable.     - Thank you.
瑞秋 你坐这边 威尔 你坐到那边去
Uh, Rachel? Why don't you sit here? And, Will, you sit way over there.
就那样 即使没有人帮我 我也可以吃掉它 没问题
That's it? Even if nobody helps me, I can eat that, no problem.
至少给我一点挑战
At least give me a challenge.
这是钱德的鸡肉
This is Chandler's chicken.
这才是火鸡
This is the turkey.
那有多大呢
Oh. How big is that?
- 大约19磅   - 它跟我刚出生时差不多大
- About 19 pounds.     - It's like me when I was born.
谁想吃地瓜泥 威尔
All right, who would, uh, like some yams? Will?
你喜欢那样做 对吧
Oh, you'd like that, wouldn't you?
什么  拜托把鸡肉…
What? Oh, you know what? Can we please keep the chicken...
跟火鸡放到另一边去
...and the turkey and everything on the other side?
- 那个味道真的…   - 太典型了
- The smell is just... Yuck.     - Typical. Ahem.
- 什么    - 我说那太典型了
- I'm sorry, what?     - I said it was typical.
你的典型作风 瑞秋女王
Typical of you, Rachel Green.
瑞秋女王在瑞秋王国想做什么就做什么
Queen Rachel, does whatever she wants in her little Rachel-land.
说真的 这家伙是谁
Seriously, who is this guy?
抱歉 你对我有问题吗
Um, ahem, sorry, do you have a problem with me?
- 我不知道 我有吗    - 我想你有
- I don't know. Do I? Do I?     - I think you do.
你在高中时对他有点凶
Apparently you were a little mean to him in high school.
- 有点凶 你让我活在痛苦深渊   - 我不知道 抱歉
- A little mean? You made my life miserable.     - I had no idea. I'm sorry.
你应该抱歉的 去他的 把地瓜泥拿过来给我
Well, you should be. Screw it. Bring on the yams.
但你很努力在减肥
Will, but you've worked so hard.
- 地瓜泥   - 好的
- Yams!     - Okay.
不论在高中时我对你做了什么
Uh, Will, I just wanna say that I'm real sorry fo...
我都非常抱歉
whatever I did to you in high school.
不只是我 我们组了一个社团
Oh, it wasn't just me. We had a club.
- 你们组了一个社团    - 没错
- You had a club?     - That's right.
"我恨瑞秋·葛林社"
The "I Hate Rachel Green Club."
你们全都聚在一起恨我
Oh, my God. So, what, you all just joined together to hate me?
- 还有谁加入那个社团    - 我跟罗斯
- Who else was in this club?     - Me and Ross.
你不必指我 她知道罗斯是谁
No need to point. She knows who Ross is.
- 你参加"我恨瑞秋社"    - 没错
- So you were in an "I Hate Rachel" club?     - Yes, he was.
不 不
No, no.
还有谁参加了你们的社团
So who else was in this club?
那个来自泰国的交换学生
Uh, actually, there was also that exchange student from Thailand.
但我想他不知道那是怎么一回事
But I don't think he knew what it was.
罗斯 我们交往了两年 你没有告诉我
So, Ross, we went out for two years and you never told me...
你参加过"我恨瑞秋社"
...you were in an "I Hate Rachel Club."
你跟她交往过 我们说好的
You went out with her? We had a pact.
那不是永久的约定
It was in high school. It's not like it was binding forever.
我们的确说了"永远"
Then why did it have the word "eternity" in it?
摩妮卡 你知道这件事吗
Okay, Monica, did you know about this?
我不知道 所以你们才会
I swear I didn't. Hey, is that why you guys...
常把房门锁上吗
...used to go up to your bedroom and lock the door?
- 对   - 我得说我松了一口气
- Yeah.     - Huh. A little relieved, I gotta say.
听着 瑞秋 我很抱歉 好吗 那时我是个愚蠢的孩子
Look, Rach, I'm sorry, okay? I was a stupid kid, okay?
我会加入社团是因为…
The only reason I joined...
- 是一起成立   - 一起成立
- Cofounded.     - Cofounded.
我会一起成立那个社团 因为我那时疯狂地爱着你
Cofounded the club, was that I was insanely in love with you.
我处理的不好
Obviously I didn't handle it very well...
如果你把"我恨瑞秋社"…
...but if you think about it, the "I Hate Rachel Club"...
想成"我爱瑞秋社"
...was really the "I Love Rachel Club."
但它真的是 "我恨瑞秋社"
Uh, except that it was really the "I Hate Rachel Club."
你们一起说我的坏话
Okay, so, what, you guys would just get together and say mean things about me?
- 不只是那样   - 不
- Well, we did a little more than that.     - No, no. No, no. No, no. Heh.
你们还做了什么
What? What else did you do?
- 我们散布一个谣言   - 什么谣言
- We started a rumor.     - What rumor?
快点 威尔 挣脱束缚告诉我们
Oh, come on, Will. Just take off your shirt and tell us.
- 罗斯   - 那真的没什么
- Ross?     - Ugh, it was no big deal.
我们说…那个谣言是…
Uh, we... We said that... The rumor was that, um...
你同时有男性跟女性的生殖器官
...you had both male and female reproductive parts.
- 什么    - 没错 我们说你爸妈…
- What?     - That's right.
丢铜板决定
We said your parents flipped a coin...
把你当成女孩养大 但你还是有小鸡鸡
...decided to raise you as a girl, but you still had a hint of a penis.
- 天啊   - 那是你们编的
- Oh, my God.     - You started that?
- 你也听过    - 我们学校里每个人都听过
- What, you heard that?     - Everyone at our school heard it.
我的学校里每个人都听过 你就是那个双性啦啦队员
Everybody at my school heard it. You were the hermaphrodite cheerleader?
噢 不
Oh, no.
现在我终于懂了
Oh, my God, this is all making so much sense to me now.
所以亚当·卡特不想跟我约会
This is why Adam Carter wouldn't go out with me.
为什么比利只想停留在这一区
This is why Billy Tratt would just stay in this region.
比利成了男同志 所以那不是我们的错
Actually, Billy Tratt is gay now, so that one's not really our fault.
- 你为什么不告诉我    - 我想或许那是真的
- Monica, how come you never told me this?     - I thought it might be true.
我担心你会大哭 把它掏出来给我看
And I was afraid that you were gonna cry and then show it to me.
别看了 那里面没有东西 那不是真的
Joey, stop staring. There's nothing there. It's not true.
- 恐怕我需要证据   - 噢…
- I'm afraid I'm gonna need proof.     - Oh...
你是我的圣母峰
You are my Everest.
- 你不必吃完它   - 我要 不然接下来是什么
- Joey, you don't have to finish that.     - Oh, yes, I do. Otherwise, what's next?
今天我吃不完一只火鸡
Today I'm just a guy who can't finish a turkey...
明天我只能吃一半的三明治…
...but tomorrow I'm the guy who eats half a Power Bar...
把刚下的东西包起来 放在冰箱 不
...wraps up the rest and puts it in the fridge? No.
我得去换条裤子 我在想什么 牛仔裤根本没有伸缩性
I just gotta change my pants. What was I thinking? Jeans have no give.
你们看史恩·麦马洪在我的纪念册上写了什么
Okay. Okay. Listen to what Sean McMahon wrote in my yearbook senior year.
"亲爱的瑞秋 你真是个好人" 我不是女孩 我是"人"
"Dear Rach, you're such a great person." Not girl, "person."
我想你太敏感了
Rach, I think you're reading a little too much into it.
"你是个好人 关于你有小鸡鸡的事我很遗憾"
"Dear Rach, you're a great person. Sorry about your teeny weenie."
你要我怎么做 你要我…
What do you want me to do...
打电话给全校的人 告诉他们那不是真的
...call everyone in the entire school and tell them it wasn't true?
- 对   - 顺便告诉他们我变瘦了
- Yes.     - Could you also tell them I'm skinny now?
还有我
Oh. Me too.
我不会打电话给任何人 那是很久以前的事了
Now, look, I'm not calling anybody, okay? It was like a million years ago.
我不在乎 你们告诉大家我是双性人
I don't care how long ago it was. You told people that I was half and half.
在高中时
You know what? I just wanna point out...
我没有做过任何伤害你的事
...I never did anything to hurt you in high school.
那不完全是真的
That's not totally true.
- 什么    - 什么
- What?     - What?
你告诉大家罗斯…
Well, you did start that rumor about Ross...
跟50岁大的图书馆员亚特曼太太亲亲抱抱
...making out with Mrs. Altmann, our 50-year-old librarian.
你怎么知道那个的
How did you know that?
- 那是真的    - 不
- It's true?     - No.
不 那是真的 我看到你们躲在书卡柜的后面
Yes, it is. I saw you guys going at it behind the card catalog.
亚特曼太太 她在…
Mrs. Altmann? She also made out...
塔塔卡奇奇回泰国前一晚 也跟他耳鬓厮磨了一下
...with Ta-Taka-Ki-Kek the night before he went back to Thailand.
高中时 你跟50岁的女人耳鬓厮磨
I'm sorry, when you were in high school you made out with a 50-year-old woman?
- 她看起来不像50岁了   - 她看起来像16岁吗
- Hey, she didn't look 50.     - Did she look 16?
事实上纪念册里有她的照片
Oh, there's a picture of her in the yearbook actually.
噢
Oh.
- 哇   - 她不太上相
- Wow.     - She didn't photograph well.
或者她不知道该怎么…
She probably wasn't familiar with the process...
花时间练习坐下来当油画模特儿
...having spent most of her life sitting for oil paintings.
这是怎么发生的  她一放学就请你吃晚餐引诱你
So how did this happen? Did she lure you to an early-bird dinner?
有一天下午我在图书馆里看书看得很晚
I was working late in the library one afternoon.
馆里只有我们两个
It was just the two of us.
她需要人帮忙玩填字游戏
She needed some help with her word jumble.
事情很自然就发生了
And one thing led to another.
我得告诉你们 安妮塔非常仁慈温柔
If you must know, Anita was very gentle and tender.
希望她能得到安息
May she rest in peace.
- 她不是拄着拐杖走路吗    - 只有在天气潮湿时
- Didn't she walk with a cane?     - Only when it was damp.
我不相信你告诉大家这件事 大家都知道吗
I can't believe you told people about this. Everybody knew?
- 好了 我要重回社团   - 耶
- You know what? I'm back in the club.     - Yeah!
- 我要加入   - 菲比
- I wanna join.     - What...? Phoebe?
抱歉 我从来没有加入过社团 我没有念过高中
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I never got to be in a club. I didn't go to high school.
但我们三个可以躲在垃圾箱后面学法文
But three of us would meet behind a Dumpster to learn French.
好吧 你们可以继续那个愚蠢的小社团
All right, you know, fine, you guys can have your stupid little club.
但你对我做的事比我对你做的事更糟糕
But I would just like to say what you did to me is way worse than what I did to you.
- 你说我有小鸡鸡   - 对
- You gave me a teeny weenie.     - Ha, ha, yeah.
你真的太傻了
All right, listen. You're just being silly.
瑞秋 即使有那个谣言 你还是最受欢迎的女孩
Rachel, even with that rumor you were one of the most popular girls in school.
大家都希望能跟你一样
Everyone wanted to be like you.
有个女孩太想变得跟你一样 她把棒条糖塞进裤档里
One girl wanted to be like you so much, she stuffed her pants with a Tootsie Roll.
罗斯 要不是她的谣言
And, Ross, if it weren't for Rachel's rumor...
没有人会知道你是谁
...I mean, no one in high school would have even known who you were.
- 是她让你成名   - 以老女人的情人成名
- She put you on the map.     - As a romancer of the elderly.
可以看得出来亚特曼太太 她以前很漂亮
Hey, Mrs. Altmann was the kind of woman you could tell she used to be pretty.
她的眼睛还是会发光
The eyes did still sparkle.
这是很久以前的事了 你们也经历过很多事
Hey, guys, this stuff is so way in the past. You've been through so much since then.
你们的未来还有许多更重要的事
And right now, you got so much more important stuff going on in your lives.
你们不能忘了这件事吗
Can't you just let this go?
她说的对
She's right.
我们的孩子快出生了
Yeah, I mean, we are having a baby together.
等一下
Hold on.
- 你让她怀孕了    - 对
- You got her pregnant?     - Yeah.
- 你们要结婚了    - 不
- Are you getting married?     - No.
你搞大她的肚子 但你不娶她
So you knocked her up but you're not gonna marry her.
兄弟
Dude.
- 有人要吗    - 好吧
- Anybody?     - Okay.
它跟我想像中完全一样
It's exactly how I imagined it would be.
好吧 火鸡在哪里
All right, where's that turkey?
- 那是我的孕妇裤   - 不 这是我的感恩节裤
- Joey, those are my maternity pants.     - No, these are my Thanksgiving pants.
好了 我吃完了
Well, that's it. I'm done.
留下了肉汗
Here come the meat sweats.
乔伊 我们非常以你为荣
Well, Joey, we're all very proud of you.
我相信总统随时都会打电话来
Yes, I believe we can expect a call from the president any moment now.
- 有什么可以帮忙的吗 - 不必了 但千万别压我的胃
- Is there anything we can do for you?     - No, just nobody press on my stomach.
还有 那条裤子你不用还了
You can keep those pants, by the way.
那是什么 那是派吗
What...? What do you got there? What is that, pie?
- 对 你要吃一点吗    - 切一小块给我就行了
- Heh. Yeah, you want some?     - Just cut me a little sliver.
大一点
A little bigger.
再大一点
Little bigger.
你害怕没派吃吗 切一大块给我
What, are you afraid you're gonna run out? Cut me a real piece.